Thanks Raido, with that in mind let's add
谢谢 Raido，有了这种概念之后，让我们添加
a Refresh Menu button to our app. For temporary
一个刷新菜单按钮在我们的app上。只是临时
purposes only though, otherwise Raido would be mad at
使用一下，否则 Raido 会生我们的气。
us. On Android, menu options are defined in XML
在ANdroid上，菜单的选项是定义在XML里面的，
and they can be declared for fragments or
而且他们可以在fragments或者是activities里面
activities. When the fragment or activity is created, it
声明。当fragment或者是activity创建的时候，它会
inflates this XML into the actual menu items in
把把XMl充实成为一个真正的菜单项，在app
the app. You'll see that there are Action buttons
里面。你可以看到这里有一些Action buttons，它们
which are menu items that appear in the Action bar,
就是出现在Action bar上面的菜单项，
such as this Search Menu item. This space is reserved
比如这个搜索菜单项。这个地方是保留给
for the most prominent actions in your app. Then anything
你app中最显著的活动的。然后其余不是很重要的菜单项，
else that's less important falls into the overflow menu by
将会布局到浮动菜单上，
tapping on this button with the three dots. These menu
通过单击这个标记了三个点按钮你就能看到它们。
items are ordered from most frequently used to least frequently
这些菜单项是按照最常用到最不常用的方式来布局的。
used. And on larger devices that have more screen real
在大一点的设备商，因为有着更多的屏幕区域，
estate, you can specify that some of these menu items can
你可以制定这其中的菜单项，把它们放到
actually go into the Action bar if there's room. If
Action bar里面，如果有空间的话。
you go back to our project in the Resources folder
如果你会过来看下我们项目的资源目录，这里，
which is called res, there is a Menu folder and
叫做res，这里有一个菜单文件夹，
inside that there's a main.xml file. If you open that up
在里面有一个main.xml的文件。如果你打开这个文件，
you see the menu layout XML, and that there's a
你可以看到菜单的XML布局，而在其中
single menu option defined for Settings. It will never show up
有一个单独的菜单选项定义在Settings里面。它不会在
as an action in the Action bar, meaning that it
Action bar里面作为一个Action来显示，也就是说，
will be in the Overflow menu. You can verify this by
它会被放在浮动菜单上，你可以通过在手机上查看你的app
checking the app on your phone. To define the ordering
来确定这一点。来定义菜单项的顺序，
of menu items, you can just add multiple items to this
你可以加入多个项目到这个XML文件里面，
XML file, and then they will show up in that order
然后它们会显示在app里面，以你定义的顺序。
in the app. If you don't like the order though, and
如果你不喜欢这种顺序，而
you want to explicitly set it, then you can specify
你想要明确的设置它们，你可以在
this order in Category, value. Right now it's set as 100,
Category里面指定其顺序，数值。目前设置的是100，
so that the Settings menu will be at the bottom of
所以Settings菜单就会出现在所有的
all the other menu options that we define in our app.
别的菜单选项的最下面，
The only Menu option that should show up below the Settings
而其中只有一个菜单项出现在Settings菜单的下面，
menu is the Help menu. Check out the link for more details.
就是Help菜单。请查看这里的链接来了解细节。